MOUSAB ELAWAD

CONTACT



Montörvägen 15, Bromma 16831



(1) +4670 515 7998



musab.abuyzed@gmail.com

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Node.js
- Maintaining and developing databases
- Sales-module (monitoring program for businesses)
- Marketing and communications

LANGUAGES

- Arabic (native)
- English (fluent)
- Chichewa (fluent)
- Swedish (basic knowledge)

Ambitious frontend development student at Hyper Island with a background in computer engineering who have gathered broad experience from various industries and countries. Not afraid to try new areas of work, genuinely passionate about digital solutions.

EXPERIENCE

May 2022 - Current

Chef O'learys Ekerö and Nortull, Stockholm

• Preparing lunch and dinner in a team with other chefs.

January 2020 - September 2021

Restaurant and Event Manager Edish Bistro, Mbabane, Eswatini

• Hired and trained staff, planned menus and invented stock, oversaw cost and expenditures to align with budget.

January 2016 - June 2019

Country Manager JPC Trade, Malawi

- Overall responsibility for the Malawi branch involving the full business cycle, from importing the cars to reaching the costumers
- Develop strategies for the company to increase sales including marketing strategies as well as capacity building of staff

December 2012 - December 2016

Marketing Manager SBT Japan, Malawi

- In charge of all marketing and advertisement in Malawi including social media and digital platforms.
- Developed and establish a call centre to expand the operations

May 2010 - November 2012

Depot Manager Petroda

- Responsible for 30 staff members including salaries and hiring
- Controlling the daily in and out-going stocks, report to the owner regarding supply, demand and general activities
- Budgeting and planning including writing financial and monitoring reports to the management board of Petroda.

EDUCATION

August 2023 - present

Frontend Development Diploma

Hyper Island, Stockholm

• HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React with an emphasis on collaborative processes with both industry actors and other developers and designers. Basic training in backend development. See portfolio.

2007-03

Diploma of Higher Education in Computer Engineering University of Gezira, Al-Gezira, Sudan

• Statistics and Probability, Mathematics, Softwear Engineering, Programming, Data security and Transmission, Data structure